sport.co.uk 2008-10-11

# Privacy Policy | Sport.co.uk

Sport.co.uk > Privacy Policy

## Privacy Policy

Media Corporation plc (�Sport.co.uk�) is committed to protecting its users� privacy. This Privacy Policy (the �Privacy Policy�), as set forth below, covers Sport.co.uk(�Sport.co.uk� or the �website�) and applies solely to information collected on Sport.co.uk. Please read this Privacy Policy to understand how we will treat personally and non-personally identifiable information we collect on Sport.co.uk. This Privacy Policy may change from time to time, so please check back periodically.

## What personally identifiable information is collected from me?

We recognise the importance of protecting the privacy of personally identifiable information collected about visitors to the Site. Except with respect to certain designated elements of the Site that require registration, you can use Sport.co.ukwithout divulging any personally identifiable information, including your email address. The Site does not collect personally identifiable information about you unless you expressly provide such information to us on a voluntary basis. For example, you may provide your personally identifiable information to subscribe to a magazine, to complete contest entry forms, to complete your registration on the Site or the various services offered on the Site, including community postings such as the Sport.co.uk Community, chats and bulletin boards. Except as described below, in those instances in which you �opt-in� to receive offers directly from our third party partners, such personally identifiable information will never be shared with third parties outside of Sport.co.uk and its affiliated companies or third party vendors acting on their behalf. 

At any time after providing us with your personally identifiable information, you have the ability to ask that your personally identifiable information be edited or removed from our database by contacting us at the e-mail or physical address provided below under the heading �Contact Information.� We may, from time to time, give you the opportunity to receive special offers, such as newsletters, email reminders or special discounts, directly from companies with which we partner. In order to take advantage of these opportunities, you must affirmatively authorise us to share your personally identifiable information with these third party partners; we will never share such information unless you specifically �opt-in� to receive such an offer from one of our partners. Similarly, as part of certain sweepstakes entries we may also give you the opportunity to sign up to receive special offers from our advertising partners. Again, during the entry process, your information will be shared with our partners only if you take specific action to indicate that you would like us to do so. 

You may choose to provide us with the certain personally identifiable information when using the Site or the various services offered on the Site, including: 

  * Your name 
  * Online contact information (email address)

In addition, at times, we may ask you to provide non-personally identifiable information about yourself that may be linked with your personally identifiable information you provide. Provision of this information is optional. Such information includes: 

Survey answers (comments, votes and ratings of Sport news/headlines or Videos) 

## What non-personally identifiable information is collected automatically?

We automatically collect certain non-personally identifiable information from you to optimize our web pages for your computer such as: 

  * clickstream information (internet protocol (�IP�) address, internet service provider, platform type, date/time stamp) http protocol information (last URL requested and browser type)
  * interaction information (browser interaction such as when the mouse moves over an image) 
  * computer information (computer and browser information)
  * search terms (search text)

We will use personally identifiable information that you submit to the Site for the purposes for which you submitted it, including marketing directly to magazine subscribers. At the time you provide personally identifiable information, you have the option of instructing us not to send you our special email offers, and of affirmatively consenting to receiving email offers about our partners. At any time, you can change these choices by visiting the My Profile page on Sport.co.ukor contacting us at the email or physical address listed in �Contact Information� below. We retain personally identifiable information indefinitely unless you request that we remove your personally identifiable information from our database by contacting us at the addresses listed in �Contact Information� below. Magazine subscribers may receive marketing information via telephone or physical address, whether they registered for a magazine on our Site, or through other means. 

We may disclose personally identifiable information when required by law or when we have a good faith belief that such action is necessary to comply with a current judicial proceeding, court order, government investigation or legal process. 

We may use non-personally identifiable information collected on the Site to enhance the Site and our product offerings, to maintain and secure the Site, and to understand the interests of Site visitors. Generally, we use non-personally identifiable information to analyze trends, administer the website, and gather information for aggregate use (IP addresses are not linked to personally identifiable information). 

We may also use the statistical compilation and aggregation of non-personally identifiable information and may provide such information to third parties for marketing, advertising or research purposes. 

We may also disclose your personally identifiable information to any third party as we, in our sole discretion, believe necessary or appropriate, in connection with a merger or consolidation with such third party or the sale of some or all of our assets, provided that such third party agrees to comply with the then-current version of this Privacy Policy. 

How is my information kept secure? We maintain commercially reasonable safeguards to ensure the security, integrity and privacy of personally identifiable information submitted to our Sites, and we periodically review and update security measures in light of current technologies. 

## What are cookies and how are they used by the Sites?

Cookies are files that a web site places on an individual�s hard-drive for record-keeping purposes. Cookies, which are an industry standard used by most web sites, can facilitate a user�s ongoing access to and use of a site. They aid the function of the Site by matching users with stored information in our database to provide personalized features. 

Our cookies cannot be used to run programs or deliver viruses to your computer. Cookies are uniquely assigned to you, and can only be read by a web server in the domain that issued the cookie to you. We will not share or sell non-aggregated information contained within cookies with any third party. The cookie itself does not contain any personally identifiable information. 

If you do not want information collected through the use of cookies, there is a simple procedure in most browsers that allows you to deny or accept the cookie feature, but you should note that cookies may be necessary to provide you with such special features as customised content delivery. Cookies can be removed from your computer by following Internet browser �help� file directions. 

## What do I need to know about third party sites, co-branded sites, and Sport.co.uk�s online business partners?

We have established relationships that allow visitors to the Site to go directly to sites operated by third parties. Some of these sites may be co-branded with our logos; however, they are not operated or maintained by Sport.co.uk. We are not responsible for the content or practices of web sites operated by third parties that are linked to the Site. These links are meant for the user�s convenience only. Links to third party sites do not constitute our sponsorship, endorsement or approval of the content, policies or practices of such third party sites. Once you have left the Site via such a link, you should check the applicable privacy policy of the third party site. 

We may use third parties to manage sweepstakes, games, contests, chats or other features, and these parties may have access to personally identifiable information submitted by visitors who participate in those activities. To the extent third parties assist us in administering sweepstakes, games, contests, chats or other features, they are acting as our agents, and have agreed to adhere to this Privacy Policy and will not use the data for any purposes other than delivering the services required for these special features. 

## Does Sport.co.uk use Third Party Ad Servers?

We use third party advertising companies and advertising networks to deliver advertisements on the Site. These companies may use cookies, web beacons, clear .gifs or similar technologies to help present such advertisements, and to help measure and research the advertisements� effectiveness. The use of these technologies by these companies is subject to their own privacy policies and is not covered by this Privacy Policy. If you would like more information about this practice please visit www.networkadvertising.org. 

## Changes to this Privacy Policy

We will occasionally update this Privacy Policy. When we do, we will also revise the �last updated� date at the bottom of the Privacy Policy. For material changes to this Privacy Policy, we will notify you by placing a prominent notice on the Site. We will not materially alter the use of your personally identifiable information without contacting you directly and seeking your affirmative consent. 

## Contact Information

You can review and update your personally identifiable information (such as e-mail) by contacting us at info@sport.co.uk or at the physical address listed below. You may also request that we remove your personally identifiable information from our database. 

If you have any questions or comments about this Privacy Policy, please contact us at:   
Sport.co.uk Customer Service   
77 Queen Victoria St   
London, EC4V 4AY   
E-mail: info@sport.co.uk 

**Privacy Policy Last Updated Date:** Wed 30th January 2008 

FREE SPORT.CO.UK E-NEWSLETTER 

Live Results

These results will be updated in     seconds.

No matches today Today - 11 October 2008   
---  
0 / 0 < >  
  
Sports Betting 

Latest Poll 

Do England have what it takes to win the World Cup?

Yes  
No

Hot Sport Babe of the Week 

 **Spike it like it's hot**  
This week sport.co.uk was in Brazil catching up with Denise Johns who we’ve officially crowned our new favourite British beach volleyball...  

Transfer Tittle Tattle 

 **Arsene wants Afellay at Arsenal**  
Arsenal are ready to make a move for Dutch international Ibrahim Afellay in January. The 22-year-old...  read more
